so let's see if we can use load Link
store conditional to implement a log
function the log
function takes a reference to variable
lockar and then in assembler and then it
will do something like this put one in
R1 load the current value of lockware
into R2 using a load link and then store
R1 into lockar using store conditional
so the idea is that we load the current
value of the log and then we store a one
there so the question for you is what do
we put here to complete this log
function in a way that works correctly
that is if we leave this function we
know that we have acquired the lock and
we are the only ones that did so the
first option for where the question mark
is is simply to do a branch on equal Z
R1 trilock the second choice here is
branch on equal Z R2
trog the third choice is to do Branch
not equal 0 R2 trog and then branch on
equals z link trilock the fourth option
is brancher not equal 0 R2 trilock and
then branch on equal 0 R1 trock and the
fifth final option is to do branch on
not equal 0 and R2 to trock followed by
a branch or not equal Z link trilock so
select which one of this five is the
correct thing to put here